Frank Stick Papers and Artwork PC.5089
Frank Stick Papers and Artwork
- Artwork, circa 1910s-1966; 45506; Stick, Frank
  - Fish Watercolors, UNK; 7956; 33GRF-1; 5000.4.570; PC.5089; Painting; Stick, Frank
    - Pollock, Pollachius virens, PC.5089.1.050; Stick, Frank (Item Pollock, Pollachius virens)
    - White Spotted Soapfish, Rypticus maculatus, PC.5089.1.051; Stick, Frank (Item White Spotted Soapfish, Rypticus maculatus)
    - Spiny Dogfish, Squalus acanthias, PC.5089.1.052; Stick, Frank (Item Spiny Dogfish, Squalus acanthias)
    - African Pompano, Alectis ciliaris, PC.5089.1.053; Stick, Frank (Item African Pompano, Alectis ciliaris)
    - Night Shark, Carcharhinus signatus, PC.5089.1.054; Stick, Frank (Item Night Shark, Carcharhinus signatus)
    - Sea Catfish, Arius felis, PC.5089.1.055; Stick, Frank (Item Sea Catfish, Arius felis)
    - Atlantic Cod, Gadus morhua, PC.5089.1.056; Stick, Frank (Item Atlantic Cod, Gadus morhua)
    - American Eel, Anguilla rostrata, PC.5089.1.057; Stick, Frank (Item American Eel, Anguilla rostrata)
    - Deepwater Chimera, Hydrolagus affinis, PC.5089.1.058; Stick, Frank (Item Deepwater Chimera, Hydrolagus affinis)
    - Haddock, Melanogrammus aeglefinus, PC.5089.1.059; Stick, Frank (Item Haddock, Melanogrammus aeglefinus)
    - Gafftopsail Catfish, Bagre marinus, PC.5089.1.060; Stick, Frank (Item Gafftopsail Catfish, Bagre marinus)
    - Spotted Hake, Urophycis regius, PC.5089.1.061; Stick, Frank (Item Spotted Hake, Urophycis regius)
    - Pilot Fish, Naucrates ductor, PC.5089.1.062; Stick, Frank (Item Pilot Fish, Naucrates ductor)
    - Jackknife-fish, Equetus lanceolatus, PC.5089.1.063; Stick, Frank (Item Jackknife-fish, Equetus lanceolatus)
    - Nurse Shark, Ginglymostoma cirratum, PC.5089.1.064; Stick, Frank (Item Nurse Shark, Ginglymostoma cirratum)
    - Lookdown, Selene vomer, PC.5089.1.065; Stick, Frank (Item Lookdown, Selene vomer)
    - Brown Shark, Carcharhinus plumbeus, PC.5089.1.066; Stick, Frank (Item Brown Shark, Carcharhinus plumbeus)
    - Yellowtail Snapper, Ocyurus chrysurus, PC.5089.1.067; Stick, Frank (Item Yellowtail Snapper, Ocyurus chrysurus)
    - White Perch, Morone americana, PC.5089.1.068; Stick, Frank (Item White Perch, Morone americana)
    - Dusky Squirrelfish, Adioryx verillarius, PC.5089.1.069; Stick, Frank (Item Dusky Squirrelfish, Adioryx verillarius)
    - Goldfish, Carassius auratus, PC.5089.1.070; Stick, Frank (Item Goldfish, Carassius auratus)
    - Coney, Epinephelus fulvus, PC.5089.1.071; Stick, Frank (Item Coney, Epinephelus fulvus)
    - Jewfish, Epinephelus itajara, PC.5089.1.072; Stick, Frank (Item Jewfish, Epinephelus itajara)
    - Black Grouper, Mycteroperca sp., PC.5089.1.073; Stick, Frank (Item Black Grouper, Mycteroperca sp.)
    - Speckled Hind, Epinephelus drummondhayi, PC.5089.1.074; Stick, Frank (Item Speckled Hind, Epinephelus drummondhayi)
    - White Shark, Carcharodon carcharias, PC.5089.1.075; Stick, Frank (Item White Shark, Carcharodon carcharias)
    - Gag, Mycteroperca microlepis, PC.5089.1.076; Stick, Frank (Item Gag, Mycteroperca microlepis)
    - Banded Rudderfish, Seriola zonata, PC.5089.1.077; Stick, Frank (Item Banded Rudderfish, Seriola zonata)
    - Black Drum, Pogonias cromis, PC.5089.1.078; Stick, Frank (Item Black Drum, Pogonias cromis)
    - Porgy, Calamus sp., PC.5089.1.079; Stick, Frank (Item Porgy, Calamus sp.)
    - Northern Puffer, Sphoeroides maculatus, PC.5089.1.080; Stick, Frank (Item Northern Puffer, Sphoeroides maculatus)
    - White Grunts with Porkfish, Haemulon plumieri, Anisotremus virginicus, PC.5089.1.081; Stick, Frank (Item White Grunts with Porkfish, Haemulon plumieri, Anisotremus virginicus)
    - FC-129, Crevalle Jack "Cavally," Caranx hippos, PC.5089.1.082; Stick, Frank (Item FC-129, Crevalle Jack "Cavally," Caranx hippos)
    - FC-182, Irish Pompano, PC.5089.1.083; Stick, Frank (Item FC-182, Irish Pompano)
    - FC-189, Boar Grunt - Blue-Striped Grunt, haemulon sciurus, PC.5089.1.084; Stick, Frank (Item FC-189, Boar Grunt - Blue-Striped Grunt, haemulon sciurus)
    - Atlantic Sharpnose Shark, Rhizoprinodon terraenovae, PC.5089.1.085; Stick, Frank (Item Atlantic Sharpnose Shark, Rhizoprinodon terraenovae)
    - Weakfish, Cynoscion regalis, PC.5089.1.086; Stick, Frank (Item Weakfish, Cynoscion regalis)
    - Scup, Stenotomus chrysops, PC.5089.1.087; Stick, Frank (Item Scup, Stenotomus chrysops)
    - Sailor's Choice, Haemulon parrai, PC.5089.1.088; Stick, Frank (Item Sailor's Choice, Haemulon parrai)
    - Summer Flounder, Paralichthys sp., PC.5089.1.089; Stick, Frank (Item Summer Flounder, Paralichthys sp.)
    - Orange filefish, Aluterus schoepfi, PC.5089.1.090; Stick, Frank (Item Orange filefish, Aluterus schoepfi)
    - Butterfish, Peprilus triacanthus, PC.5089.1.091; Stick, Frank (Item Butterfish, Peprilus triacanthus)
    - Yellow Goatfish, Mulloidichthys martinicus, PC.5089.1.092; Stick, Frank (Item Yellow Goatfish, Mulloidichthys martinicus)
    - Rock Beauty, Holacanthus tricolor, PC.5089.1.093; Stick, Frank (Item Rock Beauty, Holacanthus tricolor)
    - Gray Angelfish, Pomacanthus arcuatus, PC.5089.1.094; Stick, Frank (Item Gray Angelfish, Pomacanthus arcuatus)
    - Yellow Perch, Perca flavescens, PC.5089.1.095; Stick, Frank (Item Yellow Perch, Perca flavescens)
    - Graysby, Epinephelus cruentatus, PC.5089.1.096; Stick, Frank (Item Graysby, Epinephelus cruentatus)
    - Amberjack, Seriola dumerili, PC.5089.1.097; Stick, Frank (Item Amberjack, Seriola dumerili)
    - White Grunt, Haemulon plumieri, PC.5089.1.098; Stick, Frank (Item White Grunt, Haemulon plumieri)
    - Southern Kingfish, Menticirrhus americanus, PC.5089.1.099; Stick, Frank (Item Southern Kingfish, Menticirrhus americanus)
    - Greater Amberjack, Seriola dumerili, PC.5089.1.100; Stick, Frank (Item Greater Amberjack, Seriola dumerili)
    - Atlantic Croaker, Micropogonias undulatus, PC.5089.1.101; Stick, Frank (Item Atlantic Croaker, Micropogonias undulatus)
    - Cusk, Brosme brosme, PC.5089.1.102; Stick, Frank (Item Cusk, Brosme brosme)
    - Tautog, Tautoga onitis, PC.5089.1.103; Stick, Frank (Item Tautog, Tautoga onitis)
    - Sea Bream, Archosargus rhomboidalis, PC.5089.1.104; Stick, Frank (Item Sea Bream, Archosargus rhomboidalis)
    - Scamp, Mycteroperca phenax, PC.5089.1.105; Stick, Frank (Item Scamp, Mycteroperca phenax)
    - Snowy Grouper, Epinephelus niveatus, PC.5089.1.106; Stick, Frank (Item Snowy Grouper, Epinephelus niveatus)
    - Coney, Epinephelus fulvus, PC.5089.1.107; Stick, Frank (Item Coney, Epinephelus fulvus)
    - Unicorn Filefish, Aluterus schoepfi, PC.5089.1.108; Stick, Frank (Item Unicorn Filefish, Aluterus schoepfi)
    - Gulf Flounder, Paralichthys albigutta, PC.5089.1.109; Stick, Frank (Item Gulf Flounder, Paralichthys albigutta)
    - Black Margate, Anisotremus surinamensis, PC.5089.1.110; Stick, Frank (Item Black Margate, Anisotremus surinamensis)
    - Spottail Pinfish, Diplodus holbrooki, PC.5089.1.111; Stick, Frank (Item Spottail Pinfish, Diplodus holbrooki)
    - Sheepshead, Archosargus probatocephalus, PC.5089.1.112; Stick, Frank (Item Sheepshead, Archosargus probatocephalus)
    - Whitebone Porgy, Calamus leucosteus, PC.5089.1.113; Stick, Frank (Item Whitebone Porgy, Calamus leucosteus)
    - Silky Shark, Carcharhinus falciformis, PC.5089.1.114; Stick, Frank (Item Silky Shark, Carcharhinus falciformis)
    - Dusky Shark, Carcharhinus obscurus, PC.5089.1.115; Stick, Frank (Item Dusky Shark, Carcharhinus obscurus)
    - Leatherjacket, Oligoplites saurus, PC.5089.1.116; Stick, Frank (Item Leatherjacket, Oligoplites saurus)
    - Bar Jack, Caranx ruber, PC.5089.1.117; Stick, Frank (Item Bar Jack, Caranx ruber)
    - Warsaw Grouper, Epinephelus nigritus, PC.5089.1.118; Stick, Frank (Item Warsaw Grouper, Epinephelus nigritus)
    - Bermuda Chub, Kyphosus sectatrix, PC.5089.1.119; Stick, Frank (Item Bermuda Chub, Kyphosus sectatrix)
    - Bluefish, Pomatomus saltatrix, PC.5089.1.120; Stick, Frank (Item Bluefish, Pomatomus saltatrix)
    - Atlantic Sturgeon, Acipenser oxyrhynchus, PC.5089.1.121; Stick, Frank (Item Atlantic Sturgeon, Acipenser oxyrhynchus)
    - Longnose Lancetfish, Alepisaurus ferox, PC.5089.1.122; Stick, Frank (Item Longnose Lancetfish, Alepisaurus ferox)
    - Channel Catfish, Ictalurus punctatus, PC.5089.1.123; Stick, Frank (Item Channel Catfish, Ictalurus punctatus)
    - Inshore Lizardfish, Synodus foetens, PC.5089.1.124; Stick, Frank (Item Inshore Lizardfish, Synodus foetens)
    - Inshore Lizardfish, Synodus foetens, PC.5089.1.125; Stick, Frank (Item Inshore Lizardfish, Synodus foetens)
    - Silver Hake, Merluccius bilinearis, PC.5089.1.126; Stick, Frank (Item Silver Hake, Merluccius bilinearis)
    - African Pompano, Alectis ciliaris, PC.5089.1.127; Stick, Frank (Item African Pompano, Alectis ciliaris)
    - Permit, Trachinotus falcatus, PC.5089.1.128; Stick, Frank (Item Permit, Trachinotus falcatus)
    - Bigeye Scad, Selar crumenophthalmus, PC.5089.1.129; Stick, Frank (Item Bigeye Scad, Selar crumenophthalmus)
    - Gray Snapper, Lutjanus griseus, PC.5089.1.130; Stick, Frank (Item Gray Snapper, Lutjanus griseus)
    - Porbeagle, Lamna nasus, PC.5089.1.131; Stick, Frank (Item Porbeagle, Lamna nasus)
    - Bull Shark, Carcharhinus leucas, PC.5089.1.132; Stick, Frank (Item Bull Shark, Carcharhinus leucas)
    - Oceanic Whitetip Shark, Carcharhinus moau, PC.5089.1.133; Stick, Frank (Item Oceanic Whitetip Shark, Carcharhinus moau)
    - Blue Striped Grunt, Haemulon sciurus, PC.5089.1.134; Stick, Frank (Item Blue Striped Grunt, Haemulon sciurus)
    - Jolthead Porgy, Calamus bajonado, PC.5089.1.135; Stick, Frank (Item Jolthead Porgy, Calamus bajonado)
    - Trunkfish, Lactophrys trigonus, PC.5089.1.136; Stick, Frank (Item Trunkfish, Lactophrys trigonus)
    - Orange Filefish, Aluterus schoepfi, PC.5089.1.137; Stick, Frank (Item Orange Filefish, Aluterus schoepfi)
    - Gray Triggerfish, Balistes capriscus, PC.5089.1.138; Stick, Frank (Item Gray Triggerfish, Balistes capriscus)
    - African Pompano, Alectis ciliaris, PC.5089.1.139; Stick, Frank (Item African Pompano, Alectis ciliaris)
    - Blacktip Shark, Carcharhinus limbatus, PC.5089.1.140; Stick, Frank (Item Blacktip Shark, Carcharhinus limbatus)
    - Short Bigeye, Pristigenys alta, PC.5089.1.141; Stick, Frank (Item Short Bigeye, Pristigenys alta)
    - Opah, Lampris guttatus, PC.5089.1.142; Stick, Frank (Item Opah, Lampris guttatus)
    - Stoplight Parrotfish, Sparisoma viride, PC.5089.1.143; Stick, Frank (Item Stoplight Parrotfish, Sparisoma viride)
    - Spanish Hogfish, Bodianus rufus, PC.5089.1.144; Stick, Frank (Item Spanish Hogfish, Bodianus rufus)
    - Atlantic Spadefish, Chaetodipterus faber, PC.5089.1.145; Stick, Frank (Item Atlantic Spadefish, Chaetodipterus faber)
    - Striped Bass, Morone saxatilis, PC.5089.1.146; Stick, Frank (Item Striped Bass, Morone saxatilis)
    - Lumpfish, Cyclopterus lumpus, PC.5089.1.147; Stick, Frank (Item Lumpfish, Cyclopterus lumpus)
    - Butter Hamlet, Hypoplectrus unicolor, PC.5089.1.148; Stick, Frank (Item Butter Hamlet, Hypoplectrus unicolor)
    - Butter Hamlet, Hypoplectrus chlorurus, PC.5089.1.149; Stick, Frank (Item Butter Hamlet, Hypoplectrus chlorurus)
    - Atlantic Spiny Lumpsucker, Eumicrotermus spinosus, PC.5089.1.150; Stick, Frank (Item Atlantic Spiny Lumpsucker, Eumicrotermus spinosus)
    - Hairy Blenny, Labrisomus nuchipinnis, PC.5089.1.151; Stick, Frank (Item Hairy Blenny, Labrisomus nuchipinnis)
    - Striped Searobin, Prionotus evolans, PC.5089.1.152; Stick, Frank (Item Striped Searobin, Prionotus evolans)
    - Pumpkinseed, Lepomis gibbosus, PC.5089.1.153; Stick, Frank (Item Pumpkinseed, Lepomis gibbosus)
    - Four Spotted Fluke - Four Spotted Flounder, Paralichthys oblongus, PC.5089.1.154; Stick, Frank (Item Four Spotted Fluke - Four Spotted Flounder, Paralichthys oblongus)
    - Doctor Fish - Blue Tang, Acanthurus coeruleus, PC.5089.1.155; Stick, Frank (Item Doctor Fish - Blue Tang, Acanthurus coeruleus)
    - Spotted Trunkfish, Lactophrys bicaudalis, PC.5089.1.156; Stick, Frank (Item Spotted Trunkfish, Lactophrys bicaudalis)
    - Banded Butterflyfish, Chaetodon striatus, PC.5089.1.157; Stick, Frank (Item Banded Butterflyfish, Chaetodon striatus)
    - Red Hind, Epinephelus guttatus, PC.5089.1.158; Stick, Frank (Item Red Hind, Epinephelus guttatus)
    - Cottonmouth Jack, Uraspis secunda, PC.5089.1.159; Stick, Frank (Item Cottonmouth Jack, Uraspis secunda)
    - Scrawled Cowfish, Lactophrys quadricornis, PC.5089.1.160; Stick, Frank (Item Scrawled Cowfish, Lactophrys quadricornis)
    - Dog Snapper, Lutjanus jocu, PC.5089.1.161; Stick, Frank (Item Dog Snapper, Lutjanus jocu)
    - Schoolmaster, Lutjanus apodus, PC.5089.1.162; Stick, Frank (Item Schoolmaster, Lutjanus apodus)
    - Pigfish, Orthopristis chrysoptera, PC.5089.1.163; Stick, Frank (Item Pigfish, Orthopristis chrysoptera)
    - Trumpet Fish, Aulostomus maculatus, PC.5089.1.164; Stick, Frank (Item Trumpet Fish, Aulostomus maculatus)
    - Amberjack, Seriola sp, PC.5089.1.165; Stick, Frank (Item Amberjack, Seriola sp)
    - FC-117, Flat Needlefish, (#171), PC.5089.1.166; Stick, Frank (Item FC-117, Flat Needlefish, (#171))
    - FC-186, Yellow Tom Tate, (#160), PC.5089.1.167; Stick, Frank (Item FC-186, Yellow Tom Tate, (#160))
    - FC-214, Rough Headed Grenadier, (#108), PC.5089.1.168; Stick, Frank (Item FC-214, Rough Headed Grenadier, (#108))
    - FC-220, Blue Hake, (#97), PC.5089.1.169; Stick, Frank (Item FC-220, Blue Hake, (#97))
    - FC-221, Long Finned Hake, (#78), PC.5089.1.170; Stick, Frank (Item FC-221, Long Finned Hake, (#78))
    - #229, PC.5089.1.171; Stick, Frank (Item #229)
    - #230, Silver Gar, PC.5089.1.172; Stick, Frank (Item #230, Silver Gar)
    - FC-101, Blue Tang, PC.5089.1.173; Stick, Frank (Item FC-101, Blue Tang)
    - FC-124, Goggle-Eyed Scad, (#48), PC.5089.1.174; Stick, Frank (Item FC-124, Goggle-Eyed Scad, (#48))
    - FC-198, Red Barred Squirrel Fish, (#175), PC.5089.1.175; Stick, Frank (Item FC-198, Red Barred Squirrel Fish, (#175))
    - FC-121, Round Scad, (#312), PC.5089.1.176; Stick, Frank (Item FC-121, Round Scad, (#312))
    - FC-122 Mackrel Scad, Decapturus mararellus, (#50), PC.5089.1.177; Stick, Frank (Item FC-122 Mackrel Scad, Decapturus mararellus, (#50))
    - FC-181-2, Gray Mojarro, Xystama cinereus, (#163), PC.5089.1.178; Stick, Frank (Item FC-181-2, Gray Mojarro, Xystama cinereus, (#163))
    - Greater Barracuda, sketch, PC.5089.1.179; Stick, Frank (Item Greater Barracuda, sketch)
    - Greater Barracuda, sketch, PC.5089.1.180; Stick, Frank (Item Greater Barracuda, sketch)
    - Greater Barracuda, sketch, PC.5089.1.181; Stick, Frank (Item Greater Barracuda, sketch)
    - Northern Sennet, sketch, PC.5089.1.182; Stick, Frank (Item Northern Sennet, sketch)
    - Northern Kingfish, Menticirrhus saxatilis, PC.5089.1.183; Stick, Frank (Item Northern Kingfish, Menticirrhus saxatilis)
    - Spinner Shark, Carcharhinus brevipinna, PC.5089.1.184; Stick, Frank (Item Spinner Shark, Carcharhinus brevipinna)
    - Whale Shark, Rhiniodon typus, PC.5089.1.185; Stick, Frank (Item Whale Shark, Rhiniodon typus)
    - Lemon Shark, Negaprion brevirostris, PC.5089.1.186; Stick, Frank (Item Lemon Shark, Negaprion brevirostris)
    - Sixgill Shark, Hexanchus griseus, PC.5089.1.187; Stick, Frank (Item Sixgill Shark, Hexanchus griseus)
    - Sand Tiger Shark, eugomphodus taurus, PC.5089.1.188; Stick, Frank (Item Sand Tiger Shark, eugomphodus taurus)
    - Blue Shark, Prionace glauca, PC.5089.1.189; Stick, Frank (Item Blue Shark, Prionace glauca)
    - Thresher Shark, Alopias vulpinus, PC.5089.1.190; Stick, Frank (Item Thresher Shark, Alopias vulpinus)
    - Finetooth Shark, Carcharhinus isodon, PC.5089.1.191; Stick, Frank (Item Finetooth Shark, Carcharhinus isodon)
    - Tiger Shark, Galeocerdo cuvieri, PC.5089.1.192; Stick, Frank (Item Tiger Shark, Galeocerdo cuvieri)
    - Smooth Dogfish, Mustelus canis, PC.5089.1.193; Stick, Frank (Item Smooth Dogfish, Mustelus canis)
    - Florida Smoothhound, Mustelus norrisi, PC.5089.1.194; Stick, Frank (Item Florida Smoothhound, Mustelus norrisi)
    - Shortfin Mako, Isurus oxyrinchus, PC.5089.1.195; Stick, Frank (Item Shortfin Mako, Isurus oxyrinchus)
    - Yellow Jack, Caranx bartholomaei, PC.5089.1.196; Stick, Frank (Item Yellow Jack, Caranx bartholomaei)
    - Frigate Makerel, Auxis thazard, PC.5089.1.197; Stick, Frank (Item Frigate Makerel, Auxis thazard)
    - Chub Makerel, Scomber japonicus, PC.5089.1.198; Stick, Frank (Item Chub Makerel, Scomber japonicus)
    - Jewfish, Epinephelus itajara, PC.5089.1.199; Stick, Frank (Item Jewfish, Epinephelus itajara)
    - FC-126, Blue Runner, PC.5089.1.200; Stick, Frank (Item FC-126, Blue Runner)
    - FC-229, Blue-back Mullet, PC.5089.1.201; Stick, Frank (Item FC-229, Blue-back Mullet)
    - Pale Spotted Eel, Ophichthus ocellatus, PC.5089.1.202; Stick, Frank (Item Pale Spotted Eel, Ophichthus ocellatus)
    - Tobacco Fish, Serranus tobacarius, PC.5089.1.203; Stick, Frank (Item Tobacco Fish, Serranus tobacarius)
    - Atlantic Herring, Clupea harengus harengus, PC.5089.1.204; Stick, Frank (Item Atlantic Herring, Clupea harengus harengus)
    - Man-o-War Fish, Nomeus gronovii, PC.5089.1.205; Stick, Frank (Item Man-o-War Fish, Nomeus gronovii)
    - Atlantic Wolfish, Anarchidas Lupus, PC.5089.1.206; Stick, Frank (Item Atlantic Wolfish, Anarchidas Lupus)
    - Redear Sardine, Harengula Humeralis, PC.5089.1.207; Stick, Frank (Item Redear Sardine, Harengula Humeralis)
    - Spot, Leiostomus xanthurus, PC.5089.1.208; Stick, Frank (Item Spot, Leiostomus xanthurus)
    - Yellow Tail Flounder, Limanda ferruginea, PC.5089.1.209; Stick, Frank (Item Yellow Tail Flounder, Limanda ferruginea)
    - Tripletail, Lobotes surinamensis, PC.5089.1.210; Stick, Frank (Item Tripletail, Lobotes surinamensis)
    - Spotted Goatfish, Pseudupeneus maculatus, PC.5089.1.211; Stick, Frank (Item Spotted Goatfish, Pseudupeneus maculatus)
    - Sergeant Major, Abudefduf saxatilis, PC.5089.1.212; Stick, Frank (Item Sergeant Major, Abudefduf saxatilis)
    - Short Bigeye, Pristigenys alta, PC.5089.1.213; Stick, Frank (Item Short Bigeye, Pristigenys alta)
    - Redfin Needlefish, Strongylura notata, PC.5089.1.214; Stick, Frank (Item Redfin Needlefish, Strongylura notata)
    - Snook, Centropomus undecimalis, PC.5089.1.215; Stick, Frank (Item Snook, Centropomus undecimalis)
    - Cero, Scomberomorus regalis, PC.5089.1.216; Stick, Frank (Item Cero, Scomberomorus regalis)
    - Northern Sennet, Sphyraena borealis, PC.5089.1.217; Stick, Frank (Item Northern Sennet, Sphyraena borealis)
    - Bigeye, Priacanthus arenatus, PC.5089.1.218; Stick, Frank (Item Bigeye, Priacanthus arenatus)
    - Skipjack Tuna, Euthynnus pelamis, PC.5089.1.219; Stick, Frank (Item Skipjack Tuna, Euthynnus pelamis)
    - Great Barracuda, Sphyraena barracuda, PC.5089.1.220; Stick, Frank (Item Great Barracuda, Sphyraena barracuda)
    - Tarpon Snook, Centropomus pectinatus, PC.5089.1.221; Stick, Frank (Item Tarpon Snook, Centropomus pectinatus)
    - Orange Filefish, Aluterus schoepfi, PC.5089.1.222; Stick, Frank (Item Orange Filefish, Aluterus schoepfi)
    - Offshore Hake, Merluccius albidus, PC.5089.1.223; Stick, Frank (Item Offshore Hake, Merluccius albidus)
    - Gray Triggerfish, Balistes capriscus, PC.5089.1.224; Stick, Frank (Item Gray Triggerfish, Balistes capriscus)
    - Red Drum, Sciaenops ocellatus, PC.5089.1.225; Stick, Frank (Item Red Drum, Sciaenops ocellatus)
    - Hogfish, Lachnolaimus maximus, PC.5089.1.226; Stick, Frank (Item Hogfish, Lachnolaimus maximus)
    - Horse-eye Jack, Caranx latus, PC.5089.1.227; Stick, Frank (Item Horse-eye Jack, Caranx latus)
    - Cobia, Rachycentron canadum, PC.5089.1.228; Stick, Frank (Item Cobia, Rachycentron canadum)
    - Bonefish, Albula vulpes, PC.5089.1.229; Stick, Frank (Item Bonefish, Albula vulpes)
    - Atlantic Shad, Alosa sapidissima, PC.5089.1.230; Stick, Frank (Item Atlantic Shad, Alosa sapidissima)
    - Rainbow Runner, Elegatis pinnulata, PC.5089.1.231; Stick, Frank (Item Rainbow Runner, Elegatis pinnulata)
    - Blue Runner, Caranx crysos, PC.5089.1.232; Stick, Frank (Item Blue Runner, Caranx crysos)
    - Chain Pickerel, Esox niger, PC.5089.1.233; Stick, Frank (Item Chain Pickerel, Esox niger)
    - Pompano Dolphin, Coryphaena equisetis, PC.5089.1.234; Stick, Frank (Item Pompano Dolphin, Coryphaena equisetis)
    - Dolphin, PC.5089.1.235; Stick, Frank (Item Dolphin)
    - King Mackerel, Scomberomorus cavalla, PC.5089.1.236; Stick, Frank (Item King Mackerel, Scomberomorus cavalla)
    - Spanish Mackerel, Scomberomorus maculatus, PC.5089.1.237; Stick, Frank (Item Spanish Mackerel, Scomberomorus maculatus)
    - Alewife, Alosa pseudoharengus, PC.5089.1.238; Stick, Frank (Item Alewife, Alosa pseudoharengus)
    - Black Drum, Pogonias cromis, PC.5089.1.239; Stick, Frank (Item Black Drum, Pogonias cromis)
    - Horse-eye Jack, Caranx latus, PC.5089.1.240; Stick, Frank (Item Horse-eye Jack, Caranx latus)
    - Blackfin Tuna, Thunnus atlanticus, PC.5089.1.241; Stick, Frank (Item Blackfin Tuna, Thunnus atlanticus)
    - Florida Pomano, Trachinotus carolinus, PC.5089.1.242; Stick, Frank (Item Florida Pomano, Trachinotus carolinus)
    - Atlantic Bonito, Sarda sarda, PC.5089.1.243; Stick, Frank (Item Atlantic Bonito, Sarda sarda)
    - Rock Hind, Epinephelus adscensionis, PC.5089.1.244; Stick, Frank (Item Rock Hind, Epinephelus adscensionis)
    - Hickory Shad, Alosa mediocris, PC.5089.1.245; Stick, Frank (Item Hickory Shad, Alosa mediocris)
    - Weakfish, Cynoscion regalis, PC.5089.1.246; Stick, Frank (Item Weakfish, Cynoscion regalis)
    - Bar Jack, Caranx ruber, PC.5089.1.247; Stick, Frank (Item Bar Jack, Caranx ruber)
    - Almaco Jack, Seriola rivoliana, PC.5089.1.248; Stick, Frank (Item Almaco Jack, Seriola rivoliana)
    - Little Tunny, Euthynnus aletteratus, PC.5089.1.249; Stick, Frank (Item Little Tunny, Euthynnus aletteratus)
    - Agujon, Tylosurus acus, PC.5089.1.250; Stick, Frank (Item Agujon, Tylosurus acus)
    - Ladyfish, Elops saurus, PC.5089.1.251; Stick, Frank (Item Ladyfish, Elops saurus)
    - Tarpon, Megalops atlantica, PC.5089.1.252; Stick, Frank (Item Tarpon, Megalops atlantica)
    - Ladyfish, Elops saurus, PC.5089.1.253; Stick, Frank (Item Ladyfish, Elops saurus)
    - Mutton Snapper, Lutjanus analis, PC.5089.1.254; Stick, Frank (Item Mutton Snapper, Lutjanus analis)
    - Bonnethead, Sphyrna tiburo, PC.5089.1.255; Stick, Frank (Item Bonnethead, Sphyrna tiburo)
    - Fat Snook, Centropomus parallelus, PC.5089.1.256; Stick, Frank (Item Fat Snook, Centropomus parallelus)
    - Crevalle Jack, Caranx hippos, PC.5089.1.257; Stick, Frank (Item Crevalle Jack, Caranx hippos)
    - White Grunt, Haemulon plumieri, PC.5089.1.258; Stick, Frank (Item White Grunt, Haemulon plumieri)
    - Smooth Puffer, Lagocephalus laevigatus, PC.5089.1.259; Stick, Frank (Item Smooth Puffer, Lagocephalus laevigatus)
    - Gulf Kingfish, Menticirrhus littoralis, PC.5089.1.260; Stick, Frank (Item Gulf Kingfish, Menticirrhus littoralis)
    - Greater Amberjack, Seriola dumerili, PC.5089.1.261; Stick, Frank (Item Greater Amberjack, Seriola dumerili)
    - Lane Snapper, Lutjanus synagris, PC.5089.1.262; Stick, Frank (Item Lane Snapper, Lutjanus synagris)
    - Large Mouth Bass, Micropterus salmoides, PC.5089.1.263; Stick, Frank (Item Large Mouth Bass, Micropterus salmoides)
    - Grouper, Mycteroperca venenosa, PC.5089.1.264; Stick, Frank (Item Grouper, Mycteroperca venenosa)
    - Queen Triggerfish, Balistes vetula, PC.5089.1.265; Stick, Frank (Item Queen Triggerfish, Balistes vetula)
    - Tarpon, Megalops atlantica, PC.5089.1.266; Stick, Frank (Item Tarpon, Megalops atlantica)
    - Agujon, Tylosurus acus, PC.5089.1.267; Stick, Frank (Item Agujon, Tylosurus acus)
    - Atlantic Cutlassfish, Trichiurus lepturus, PC.5089.1.268; Stick, Frank (Item Atlantic Cutlassfish, Trichiurus lepturus)